{
    "id": "4657bd8dc3b94552af6b200b1d217c16",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been waiting here …………….. 6 o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys are playing …………….. the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is someone ……………… the gate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ……………… her like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite happy ……………. her result.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am impressed ………………. your work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been waiting …………….. ages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We may go swimming – it depends ……………. the weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju is anxiously waiting …………… his results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is absorbed ………………. his studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}